ewatches.com 2015-12-10

# Watches, Watches for Men, Discount Watches, Women's Watches, Chronograph | eWatches | US

**Last Updated: July 16, 2008**

eWatches.com Privacy Policy

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for eWatches.com. We are committed to protecting your privacy and encourage you to periodically review this page to be informed of how we protect the information you disclose to us. 

If you believe that eWatches.com is not abiding by our posted privacy policy, please contact us at 1-866-79WATCH(92824) or email us. 

**Information Collection and Use**  
eWatches.com collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

**My Account**  
When you make a purchase on our site, you will have the option to create an account. By creating an account, the system will remember your personal and purchase information and the checkout process on future purchases will be fast, easy and secure. At your option, your account can also store important dates such as birthdays or anniversaries and allow you to subscribe to receive promotional emails and announcements from us (see “Electronic Mailings” below).

Creating an account is also fast and easy: simply enter your personal information once and select your very own username and password. Then during checkout on your next purchase, just login and the system will take care of the rest. At all times, your personal information is accessible to you to review, edit, or update as necessary by clicking on the “My Account” link. 

**Order**  
We request information from the user on our order form when making a purchase. Here is where a user must provide their contact information, like name and shipping address, and financial information, like credit card number and expiration date. This information is used for billing purposes and to fill the customer's order. If we have difficulty processing an order, this contact information is used to communicate with the customer. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. We use both session and persistent cookies. Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users in the aggregate by analyzing popular areas and products to enhance future experiences on our site.Cookies do not cause damage to your computer systems or files, and only the web site that transferred a particular cookie to you can read, modify or delete such cookie. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there are simple procedures in most browsers that allow you to delete existing cookies, to automatically decline cookies, or to be given the choice of declining or accepting the transfer of particular cookies to your computer.

**Usage Tracking**  
eWatches.com's database tracks the traffic throughout our site. This information is used to compile overall statistics and is not recorded at an individual level. This includes IP (internet protocol) addresses, browser type, ISP (internet service provider), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and #of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate. The statistics help us decide which products and services best serve our members and guests.

**Aggregate Information**  
eWatches.com uses aggregate information from demographic surveys, traffic patterns and IP addresses to customize our site. Aggregate information is occasionally shared with third parties for purposes such as planning or executing advertising or promotions.

**Sharing**  
eWatches.com gives you access to third party partners to provide you with certain services. eWatches.com will provide that third party with your transaction information and then that third party will collect additional information if needed to provide you with the requested service, such as outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services.

We reserve the right to transfer any and all information that we collect from users of the site to a third party in the event of any merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of the assets or stock (including without limitation in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings) relating to eWatches.com.

Finally, notwithstanding any other provision of this privacy policy to the contrary, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information if we believe that we are required to do so (i) by law; (ii) to comply with legal process or governmental requests; (iii) to enforce our Terms of Service; (iv) to protect our operations or those of any affiliated entities; (v) to protect the rights, privacy, safety or property of eWatches.com, any affiliated entities, you or others; and (vi) to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

**Links**  
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by eWatches.com.

**Catalog, Newsletters, Etc.**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our catalog, newsletter, etc., we ask for contact information such as name, street address and email address to provide these communications. Because we respect our users' privacy, we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the choice and opt-out section below.

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send you an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though you can deactivate your account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. 

**Surveys & Sweepstakes**  
From time to time, our site requests information from users via surveys or sweepstakes. Participation in these surveys or sweepstakes is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name, shipping address and email address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

**Tell-A-Friend**  
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about an item, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. eWatches.com will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. We do store the friend's email and they have an option to opt-out in the communication.

**Special request page**  
Our customers can use the special request page to inquire about products that they cannot find on the website, such as, for example, special orders. Personal information is gathered during this process.

**Security**  
eWatches.com takes precautions to protect our users' information. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the Secure Socket Layers (SSLs)encryption software. While on a secure page, such as our order form, a lock icon appears on the bottom of your Web browser. When you are not on a secure page, no lock icon will appear. To learn more about SSL, click here. In addition, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment under restricted access.

If you have any questions about the security at our website, send us an Online Inquiry for more info.

**Supplementation of Information**  
In order for eWatches.com to properly fulfill its obligation to our customers, it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from third party sources. When a user makes a purchase from any of these companies, the companies collect and share that purchase information with us so we can tailor the site to our users' preferences.

**Special Offers**  
Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special offers and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.

**Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate that user's personally identifiable information provided to us. This can be done by using the unsubscribe feature in our communication or by sending us an   
Online Inquiry.

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our order form has an 'opt-out' mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don't want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists.

Users who no longer wish to receive promotional materials may opt-out of receiving these communications by using the unsubscribe feature in any email.

**Changes to This Policy**  
We reserve the right to change this privacy policy, and any of our policies or procedures concerning the treatment of information collected through the site, without prior notice. You can determine when this privacy policy was last revised by referring to the "Last Updated" legend at the top of this page. Any changes to our privacy policy will become effective upon posting of the revised policy on the Internet, accessible through the site. Use of the site following such changes constitutes your acceptance of the revised policy then in effect. We encourage you to bookmark this page and to periodically review it to ensure familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy.
